{
    "subject": "resource/Amnon_Dankner",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Amnon Dankner (Hebrew: \u05d0\u05de\u05e0\u05d5\u05df \u05d3\u05e0\u05e7\u05e0\u05e8\u200e, February 5, 1946 \u2013 April 5, 2013) was an Israeli newspaper editor and author. He was the editor of the mass-circulation daily Maariv for six years.",
    "human_readable": "Amnon Dankner was an Israeli newspaper editor and author.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6509435772895813,
            "question": "What nationality was Amnon Dankner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6146470904350281,
            "question": "What was Amnon Dankner's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5897010564804077,
            "question": "What type of books might Amnon Dankner have authored?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5234194397926331,
            "question": "What kind of work might an Israeli newspaper editor produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4332612156867981,
            "question": "What did Amnon Dankner do besides writing books?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4200219511985779,
            "question": "Where was Amnon Dankner likely based during his career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4132062792778015,
            "question": "In what field was Amnon Dankner active?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3772270679473877,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Amnon Dankner's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35886481404304504,
            "question": "Name two professions that Amnon Dankner held."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26527631282806396,
            "question": "What is an example of a work created by Amnon Dankner?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Amnon Dankner was an Israeli newspaper editor and author.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6737_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name two professions that Amnon Dankner held.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6737_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Amnon Dankner's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6737_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what field was Amnon Dankner active?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6737_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6737_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6737_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6737_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6737_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6737_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6737_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6737_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6737_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6737_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6737_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that Amnon Dankner was an Israeli newspaper editor and author."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Amnon Dankner was an Israeli newspaper editor and author.\" They mention his roles as the editor of Maariv, a daily Hebrew newspaper, and his career in journalism including his work as a columnist and editor-in-chief."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}